[dramatic music playing]
[man] Hey, fucker.
Who was it?
[sighs]
Hey.
Didn't I tell ya
not to fuck around while you're working?
I mean, what the hell?
I apologize.
Hey.
[sighs] Seok-dae oppa's cousin
said someone beat him up,
so we went to help.
You decided to help,
and you got your ass kicked?
- I wouldn't exactly say he got his ass…
- [man] Shut up.
- Okay.
- [stubs out cigarette]
[grunts softly]
Let's make them pay for it.
Hmm? [grunts]
[Seok-dae grunts]
There you go!
[chuckles] Hey. We'll split it.
Yeah? I'll give you half.
- [grunting]
- [Seok-dae whimpers]
Ah! [laughs]
- [grunts]
- [crunch]
["Hero" by Meego playing]
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
[Su-ho] Look what hyeong's about to do.
- [Beom-seok] Oh!
- [Su-ho] Okay! Mark ten points.
We should be studying
for our assessment, right?
Yeah, you're right.
[Su-ho] Si-eun-ssi.
Bro, it's the weekend, yeah?
We need to let our blood circulate
so our brains can function better.
We need to have a little fun
once in a while.
- [balls clatter]
- [sighs]
You're not going to college?
Man, almost.
Climbing back into hell? Huh?
Are you literally insane?
Get up. Your turn.
[boys in background groan]
Get up and play. Don't play hard to get!
- [chuckles]
- [Su-ho] Aah! This guy.
[Si-eun sighs]
[Su-ho] Aah.
[Si-eun] Reflection principle.
The incident angle
and the reflection angle are the same
from the center of the billiard ball.
Incident angle, 35 degrees.
Margin of error, within three degrees.
Probability of success, 90%.
- [Beom-seok] Oh!
- [laughs]
[Si-eun] Let's go study.
Where are you going? We play three rounds.
A hundred points to start off. Okay?
[boys in background cheer and laugh]
I think it'll be the same result.
Ah, shit.
You think so? Huh?
You think it'll be the same?
Let's bet on jjajangmyeon and tangsuyuk.
No wait, gochu japchae. Are you in, bro?
[boys in background whoop]
[sighs]
[Su-ho] Come on!
You know I went easy on you.
- No, you didn't.
- Agh, I feel so miserable. Shit.
Whatever. Let's grab a beer.
I'm leaving. Go ahead.
Why? Let's go together. I got it.
You guys already put me behind schedule.
All right. Get home safe. It'll be us two.
You got lucky today, man.
Next time, I won't go easy on you.
- So, um, where should we go grab drinks?
- Hey, come on. Hurry up, follow me.
[PA chiming]
[man 1] Ma'am. Ma'am, please.
[muffled announcement on PA]
[man 2] Check that box, please.
[man 2] That's correct.
Hyeong, what's with your arm?
[man 3] What do you think?
It's all your fault, little hyeong.
[menacing music playing]
What?
Who are you?
[man 3 chuckles]
That's none of your business.
But I need you to do me a favor.
[upbeat pop music playing]
Fuck. What the hell's he doing here?
I'm fucked. [gasps]
[assistant 1] Can I help you
find something? Oh…
[assistant 2] It's 13,000 won.
Oppa, you almost done?
They don't have what I want.
- [assistant 2] Thank you.
- [Yeong-i] Hurry up, I'm hungry.
Thanks a lot!
Let's go.
[gasps] What? It's pouring rain out here.
Ah, man. Why's it raining so much?
Wait a sec!
I don't have an umbrella.
Uh…
- Walk me home. It's pouring.
- Why should I?
[Yeong-i] Because you have
an umbrella and I don't.
- Do you like tteokbokki?
- [Si-eun] No.
[Yeong-i] Oh. I know
a great tteokbokki place over there.
It'll change your mind.
[Yeong-i] Mmm.
It's really spicy.
[quirky music playing]
[Si-eun] Hey.
- Is it all right if I leave?
- No, you can't leave.
- Why not?
- I don't like to eat when I'm alone.
[sighs]
Why aren't you eating? Too spicy?
- Why would you eat this?
- [chuckles]
You don't have any friends, huh?
[phone bleeps]
- [ringing tone]
- [phone buzzing]
That's my number. Save it.
What's your name?
Why?
[sighs]
ASSHOLE
[sighs] Because you seem
like a selfish and rude asshole.
Guys like you are kinda my style.
Thank you for the food!
[phone ringing]
[Yeong-i] I'm gonna go. See you later.
Sorry about before.
Yeah, I'm coming.
I'm heading over now.
Uh-huh.
- [insects chirping]
- [dog barking]
[car doors close]
- Where's Yeong-i?
- [boy 1] On her way back.
- [video game gunfire]
- Go, you shit!
- Gil-su hyeung inside?
- Uh-huh.
[boy 2] Nice work.
[chuckles] Hey.
This crazy kid brought his mom's car.
- [all laugh]
- [boy 2] Idiot.
- [boy 3] Awesome.
- [boy 5] Out of his mind.
Hey, fuckin' asshole.
I told you
not to ignore my calls, didn't I?
[menacing music playing]
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
What are you going to do to pay me back?
I'll get it from my mom.
[Gil-su sighs]
I'll give you three days.
If you don't have the money by then,
your shitty parents will
be fucking dead, you got it?
Huh? And I'll burn your house down too.
[clinking]
[Gil-su sighs]
Did it go well?
Yes.
Whoa. Good job.
That little bastard.
Hey, will you beat him up for, like,
30 minutes before kicking him out?
Or you can just stab him.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[boys chatting]
- [boy 1] …study that…
- [boy 2] Yeah. Let's go.
[boy 1] …hard time sleeping, as well…
[boy 3] I don't sleep.
[boy 1] Think I'm gonna
prepare for the test.
- [boy 3] Class was rough today.
- [boy 4] Yeah. I did have a good time.
- [Beom-seok] It's coming.
- [Su-ho] Look.
- [Beom-seok] The thunder.
- [Su-ho] I see it. Right there. Ah!
- Wait, I'm gonna do this one.
- [boy 3] …it smells great. Girls…
- [Beom-seok] Su-ho-ya, the car.
- [Su-ho] Oh, yeah, the car. Get in.
- [Beom-seok] That the only one?
- Oh, here. I'll take this one instead.
- I want that one.
- Take the other one.
- Yeon Si-eun.
- [Su-ho] Hey.
[Yeong-bin] Can I talk to you
for a minute?
I don't have anything to say.
Hey, what do you want now?
I'll be real quick.
- [yawns loudly]
- Please help me out here.
Will you meet with my attorney just once?
All you have to do is just
tell him that it wasn't my fentanyl.
[yawns]
[Yeong-bin] Beom-seok, you too.
[sighs] I'm the only reason
that my mom wakes up in the morning.
[sighs] Please help me.
Or else I'll end up
going to a reformatory.
[sighing]
[Su-ho] This crying act
isn't fooling anybody.
- [Yeong-bin sobbing]
- Si-eun-a.
Shall we just make a statement?
It wouldn't be that hard.
[sighs]
[Su-ho groans]
Hey.
Why are you going to the basement?
Oh, it's a shortcut.
I'll kill you if you're lying.
I'm not lying.
[Su-ho] Hey, hurry up.
[Su-ho groans] What should
we eat for dinner?
[Si-eun] I'm going to the hagwon.
[Su-ho] Come on! You always say that.
Let's go get a bowl of jjajangmyeon
and go to the internet café later.
It's okay for you to skip work today?
Oh. Do I have work? Darn it.
[menacing music plays]
[Su-ho sighs] Guess I won't make it.
[sighs]
I expected this.
[Gil-su] Hey, little hyeongs.
Nice to meet ya.
[sighs]
Seok-dae-ya, was it them?
Yes.
[sighs]
Well, as you may know,
my dear Seok-dae had to go
to the hospital because of you.
- I mean, he doesn't even have insurance.
- [paper rustles]
Hmm? How could you beat him up like that?
What is it you want?
[Gil-su] I'll give you three days.
Bring 15 million won to me.
[scoffs]
That's bullshit. Hey.
What's up with the cast?
I never touched your arm, man.
You don't even remember
break-break-breaking his arm like this?
You little piece of shit.
[Si-eun] But
do you have evidence that it was us?
Wow!
[laughs]
Man, these little hyeongs are
freakin' wild.
Hey.
[sighs]
I kill people for less money.
Sometimes I'll break a limb if I want.
Bragging about that is childish.
This motherfucker…
[inhales]
[exhales]
Are you kidding?
[scoffs]
I'll give you three days.
If you don't bring me my money,
you'll be borrowing it from me then.
[laughs]
- [Su-ho yelps]
- [laughs] You rude little prick.
- [knife clicks]
- [Gil-su laughs]
Let's go.
[engines revving]
- [tires screeching]
- [horns honking]
Are you okay, Su-ho-ya?
- [Su-ho] Not at all. Fuck.
- [Beom-seok] Hold on.
[Su-ho] Okay.
[groans]
- [Beom-seok] What do we do?
- [Su-ho sighs]
They can't do anything. Ow, shit.
I don't know why it's not starting.
They said it'd run.
- [boy 1] Hey, yeah.
- [ringing tone]
Kids are coming out.
[tense music playing]
[boy 2] Who is this? All right.
[boy 3 spits]
[laughs]
- I'll go with you when you go.
- I'll look over it again.
[boy 4] Is that him?
Hey.
[boy 5] We're just hanging out.
[boy 6] Yeah, I could
really eat something.
[boy 5] What's he lookin' at?
- [coughs]
- [laughs] Yeah.
[tense music continues]
[horn beeping]
[lock bleeps]
[music fades]
[phone bleeps]
[ringing tone]
[Yeong-i] Hello?
Let's meet somewhere.
- [door opens]
- [shop bell rings]
[muzak playing]
[sighs] That guy.
What does he do?
Who?
Oh.
Gil-su?
[smacks lips]
[sighs] That guy lets us crash
and gives us a job.
- What kind?
- [Yeong-i] You know, this and that.
Why do you care?
[sighs]
I shouldn't be saying this.
Just watch your back 'cause he's trash.
[tense music playing]
[Yeong-i] He wasn't lying when he said
he killed people for money.
He has gangster connections. Real ones.
He's money-crazy. He's not even human.
So what?
Give him whatever money you have,
even if it's half.
[Si-eun] Otherwise?
What happens if I don't?
[sighs]
You're fucked.
You'll be fucked like the rest of us.
Will it be done?
[Yeong-i] What?
If he gets paid?
- [Yeong-i] Hmm.
- Will you be okay?
[music stops]
[suspenseful music playing]
[quiet clattering]
[exhales]
[Su-ho yawns]
Why? What's going on?
What is it?
Man, I'm hungry. Ugh.
CHEMISTRY LAB
[Su-ho yawns]
[sighs] I'll do it. I'll take care of it.
- Hmm?
- It's been three days.
[unzips bag]
Fifteen million won.
Once he has it, it'll end.
[Su-ho] What's this?
Um, it's from my parents.
Are you kidding me? Huh?
Your parents just gave you this?
Where'd you get it?
- Why does that even that matter?
- [Su-ho] Where'd you get it?
Where's it from?
I sold my father's watch.
He was handing it down to me anyway, so…
What an idiot. Huh?
Why give money to that asshole?
We can just call the police.
[sighs]
Take this and get your watch back.
They told us that going to the police
wouldn't do us any good.
Beom-seok-a.
Thanks a lot.
But I'll handle it. Don't worry about it.
[Su-ho] How the hell
are you gonna handle it?
Let's just report it.
Yeah, I'm gonna do that.
That asshole makes
runaway kids do jobs for him.
PROMISSORY NOTE
Do you know about Free Money?
It's popular with high school kids.
- What? What's that?
- A gambling site.
It gives you 50,000 won as soon
as you join, so it's called Free Money.
Gil-su's partner runs it overseas.
Everything's rigged.
They let you win the first few rounds.
You end up making tens of millions of won.
- False hope. They let you keep winning.
- [phone chimes]
That's when it happens.
You begin to lose everything that you won.
- [sad sound effect]
- [Yeong-i] Nothing is chance.
Their balance of tens of millions of won
suddenly drops to zero.
They go nuts.
So they keep gambling,
trying to win back what they lost.
But how do they keep gambling?
They lost their money.
[bleep]
[Yeong-i] Gil-su has
membership information,
so he approaches them
and offers a private loan.
All these kids obviously
can't repay the debt they owe,
so they bring collateral.
A few days ago,
someone even brought their mom's car.
He basically makes the kids steal money
and stuff from their parents.
[Si-eun] Then he takes out private loans
using the kids' bank accounts.
He makes them do dead drops for drugs.
Gets them involved in crimes,
keeping them trapped.
Their housing has ledgers,
contracts, even illegal drugs.
All we need to do is bring
the police over there.
[Beom-seok sighs]
How'd you know about all that?
Did you Google it?
Uh, I… just know.
[sighs]
[Su-ho] Well, let's do Si-eun's great plan
right after we get something to eat.
Okay? I'm so hungry, I could die!
[menacing music playing]
Hey, one sec.
[Si-eun] Why?
I'll, um… go by myself.
What?
Hey, like you said, if the ledgers
and drugs are at their place,
office, or whatever,
we have to bring the police over there.
Yeah. I'll call them right now.
No, dude. You have to catch them there.
Photos won't do any good.
So I'll go there first
and send you the address.
Come with the police. I'll stall for time.
Hey, you can't go by yourself.
I'm still the toughest guy
at Byuksan High. You don't trust me?
It's all right, 'kay? Bye.
[sighs]
[boy 1] Yeah, I think
I'm maybe gonna ask her out tonight.
[Gil-su] Hey!
You Three Musketeers disbanded?
[Su-ho] Hey, we're not
a bunch of dicks like you.
We only need one.
[sighs] Stop talking shit
and hand it over. Right now.
Before I do that,
let's have a word, man to man.
God… [splutters]
You don't have it, do you?
[chuckles]
I have something better. Hmm?
[sighs] I mean, here's the thing.
Hyeong, I'm the top dog in this school.
There's a way I can help you out here.
That gambling website of yours
can make a lot more money.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How'd you know that?
Him.
His cousin is in my class.
- He showed me the website before.
- Aah.
- [Su-ho] Mm-hmm.
Everybody gets a voucher
for 50,000 won when they join.
Instead of giving them just one,
let's do at max three vouchers per person.
Then, implement a referral system.
Pretty soon, the whole school
will be a gambling den.
I'm sure you have an office or whatever.
Let's go there, have coffee, and talk.
- [Gil-su sighs]
- How's that?
[laughs]
This little hyeong's ambitious.
[sighs] Okay, hop in.
Hey, take the wheel.
- [boy 1] Sure, hyeong.
- [Yeong-i] Oppa.
Should we wait up for the other two
and take them with us, just in case?
Yeah, sure.
Seong-chan, get in.
The youngest is coming with me.
Move it.
- [car door slides open]
- [Yeong-i sighs]
[Su-ho] Oh!
[sighs]
[boy 2 grunts]
[chuckles]
[Su-ho exhales]
[engine starts]
What's that about?
[gasps]
Hold on a minute.
- [Si-eun] They went to your place, right?
- Uh-huh. Why's he going there alone?
- You're not reporting from here?
- We'll bring the police there.
- What's the address?
- [Yeong-i sighs]
17-1 Sanggye-ro, Nowon-gu, Seoul.
It's a single-family house
with blue gates.
17-1 SANGGYE, NOWON, SEOUL
HOUSE WITH BLUE DOOR
[Beom-seok] Hey, taxi. Taxi!
[watch buzzes]
SI-EUN: IF THE ADDRESS IS RIGHT
TEXT ANYTHING BACK
[Si-eun] Hey, hey. What are you doing?
[sighs]
Everything's gonna be okay
once I bring the money to him.
Why's Su-ho going there alone?
That guy's crazy.
What are we gonna do?
What if something happens?
Please go to 17-1 Sanggye-ro, Nowon-gu.
[sighs]
[Seok-dae] Yeong-a.
What are you doing?
[Yeong-i sighs]
[sighs]
Trying to make sure Gil-su goes to prison.
What?
He's gonna bring the police
over to our place.
If we keep going like this,
we're gonna be stuck
in this kind of life forever.
You don't want that either, right?
[Su-ho sighs]
Stay here for a little bit, okay? Huh?
Yeah, no problem.
[car door opens]
- [Su-ho] Aah.
- [car door slams]
[ominous music playing]
[Su-ho sighs]
Wow, that's a pretty house.
Blue gates. Hmm.
That's cobalt blue, right?
How pretty.
[Gil-su] Let's go.
[tense music playing]
[Gil-su sighs]
[distant sirens blaring]
[Su-ho sighs]
Sit over there. Sit. [chuckles]
[gate closes]
Ah, I like your place.
- I'm into retro.
- [Gil-su chuckles]
Something to drink?
I'd be grateful with
just a cup of water or something.
[Gil-su] Water?
Hey, give your phone to me.
- Why?
- Ah, I just want to make sure.
This, this, this, here.
I want to find out if you've
been using it or not.
I'm the type who's very sensitive
about personal information.
[laughs]
I can't work with you like that.
[both laughing loudly]
I see, yeah.
Well, you leave me no choice.
- [Su-ho grunts]
- Aah!
- [Su-ho groans]
- Give it to me.
Goddamn it, son of a bitch! Deceive me?
- Fucking son of a bitch! [yells]
- [Su-ho grunting]
Whew.
- [bat clatters to floor]
- [Gil-su] Give me his phone.
[sighs]
[sighs] "I'm on my way with the police?"
[Su-ho] Wow, that's a pretty house.
Blue gates.
[laughs] Hey. Hey!
What the hell is this?
[scoffs] I thought you'd come
with your punk friends,
but you called the fucking cops,
you asshole!
[puffing]
Hey, call Seok-dae, that motherfucker.
All of you, come with me.
[tires screech]
[breathing shakily]
[shuffling footsteps]
Hey, are you here alone?
Yes. Well, I uh, brought the…
I'm here to give you the money.
Let my friend go first,
then I'll give it to you.
Are you trying to trick me,
you little shit?
You son of a bitch. Follow me.
[siren blaring]
[tires squeal]
[siren stops]
[man sighs] This isn't even
our jurisdiction.
[bell rings]
[bleeping]
- [man on radio] What is your status?
- Is anybody here?
[banging on gate]
Anyone?
- [radio bleeps]
- Hey, kid.
- [man] On the premises yet?
- You sure this is it?
Yes.
[bleeping]
- What now?
- [man] What is your status?
- Units en route.
- Ahem.
We can't, um, really do anything, right?
[cop 1] Well, we should head out.
Next time, come to the station.
[Si-eun] What?
[cop 2] We didn't come here
with a search warrant.
There's no evidence at all,
just a few photographs.
[cop 1] We'll still hand over those photos
to the Violent Crimes Unit.
Come by the station to give
your statement sometime.
- And pick up your phone when we call.
- [cop 2 sighs]
[car doors open and shut]
[engine starts]
[car pulls away]
[suspenseful music playing]
[glass crunching]
[gasps]
AHN SU-HO
[ringing tone]
[ringing tone continues]
[Yeong-i] There's a room where
he keeps all the illegal property.
[ringing tone continues]
[Yeong-i] All the ledgers and drugs
should be in the safe.
[robotic voice] Your call
cannot be completed as dialed.
Please leave a message after the tone.
[suspenseful music continues]
["Brass Knuckle" by Boi B playing]
♪ Kick it ♪
♪ Yo, brass knuckle, do the damn, uh ♪
♪ Yo, yo… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ You never know… ♪
♪ Knock, knock… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Good boy gone bad… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ But I got K2 in my mouth… ♪
♪ Break your fuckin' neck… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Yo, smells like teen spirit… ♪
♪ Brass knuckle… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ But you don't hear me, though
Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ Pow, brass knuckle, do the damn thing ♪
♪ Good boy gone bad ♪
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL